Hello, hello friends, welcome to
your own YouTube channel Indian
Market. Today, many companies in the market are
presenting their trading numbers. Out of them, there are
some selected companies on
which you can definitely focus if you want.
I have many friends
who have open companies, so they also have to take a
decision, that is, should they close these
companies or sell them
or should they add them? So,
we will go through everything one by one. So,
let's start the video right now.
First of all, if we talk about the company,
Ambuja Cement is a selling company in this sector. If we talk about
its market cap, then
its market cap is more than Rs 70 thousand crores. If we talk about the
fundamentals of this company, then I see it strong for a long time.
Apart from this, if we talk about
its maximum chart pattern, then it continuously goes
up. The purpose of telling this in my room is that
friends, if the business of a company is
good, then we get to see the chart of that company
going up in this manner on the button.
Apart from this, if we
talk about updates, then you guys  You must have heard the updater,
this is not today's update, but to clear
your mind of half the incident,
I am repeating it again, that Gautam Adani
Office 21 126 Person of Ambuja Cement ACC
from open market, that is, you must be aware
that recently Gautam Das ji
Advani ji was seen investing in this company, so
whoever has this company
should press the NOTA button for the long term
because in the coming time,
you will see the business of this company growing at a fast pace,
due to which momentum in the stock is
a normal thing, but you people should
also have patience, if your view is
long term, then definitely this company is a
company that will go up in value, otherwise be
patient and hold, whoever has this
company should not make the mistake of sitting idle at all,
if we talk about it, thank you, thank you,
friends, today's date the numbers of this company are going to come,
so these numbers are a bit bad,
or
if the stock falls due to the little gains that you get, then
definitely you  People
should consider adding quantity and those who have got new financial gains
then definitely it is on the decline.
If you get this company then
definitely you
can consider adding quantity and only and only people should focus on the
decline of voters. You people have to
focus on this company otherwise you should
ignore it. Apart from this, if we talk about the
next company then its name is this
small finance bank, you can see it here. If we
talk about this company then its market
cap was fine, it was seen to be of about 35
thousand crores,
but friends, I
cannot say that at all, but this bank seems to be a little
risky. If you want to
go to any bank in the private sector then you can definitely consider going
with HDFC Bank, Kotak or you
can consider going with ICICI Bank. If you people are in the public sector
bank, you will get this bank,
however, if we talk about this company then
friends, it completely ignores it.
Apart from this, if we talk about the next
company then its name is  This is Control Print.
If we talk about Marg and Chauhatan of this company,
then you can see here that nothing
special is visible.
Apart from this, if we talk about this company, then
you can see that
its market cap is around Rs. 750 crores. If you
talk about this, then click on it and you will see
that it is around Rs. 4 crores, that is, it is almost negligible.
Apart from this, if we
talk about reserves, then according to the type of
market cap of the company, I got
to see good ones. Apart from this, you
can see the plug here, what does the company do?
Control Printer Limited is involved in
development, research, manufacturing and
marketing of printing machine spare
parts and consumables and also added
services. That is, you can understand that
if we talk about the business model of the company, then
I get to see features and entries.
This does not mean that you should
invest in this company. Friends,
I covered this top for this
because many marital brothers get
trapped in such companies later. So, this is
my personal belief.  You should
maintain some distance from this company, the final decision will be yours
because if you have money then
I will not say anything to those who have it,
but for a new buyer, I would advise you to maintain
distance from this company.
Apart from this, if we talk about the
people behind it, you can see that its profit is going
down, if we talk about Morena
and if we talk about it then here we can
see that it is going up, so good things, if we
talk about the profit and loss statement of this company
then you can see
that here we can see consistency, even though the
profits of big companies were less,
but we can see them continuously increasing,
which is a very good thing.
Apart from this, if we talk about its balance sheet
then you can see that whatever
we are seeing is continuously growing in a good manner, it is almost
negligible,
sometimes the company can declare itself dead at any time.
Apart from this, if we talk about promoter holding, then
I am seeing dissention in that too, the
promoters have up to 50% take
and  If we talk about the top of the face, you
can see that if we talk about the six and a half inch
device, then there has been a lot of
enthusiasm among them as well.
You can see here that
we are seeing a step of about twelve and a half percent here. The
government is also
interested in this company. Apart from this,
talking about the public, up to 28.8 percent is seen. So, those who
have this comment, it is not a bad company,
but those who want to make a new purchase, then
I feel that you people should keep a
distance from this company.
Apart from this, if we talk about the next company, then you
can see here that if we
talk about the maximum set button for this, then we can
see that it remains on the top, but you
can see here that since you started
seeing pressure in the market,
till now, the shares of this company have seen a
decline of around 40 percent.
Apart from this, if we talk about the fundamentals of this company, you
can see that
in recent times, it is seen in a midcap IT company. Apart from this, if we
talk about the debt, then approximately  Work worth around two thousand crores has been
seen, whereas when we used to
talk about around one thousand crores,
apart from this, if we talk about the
company, then you
can also read it by crossing the video here, friends, the
purpose of telling is that I feel that you people should keep a
distance from this company as well.
If we talk about its pendency, then you
people can see here that it is continuously going
up,
we can see that the profits of the company are continuously increasing,
Ajay, but if we talk about this company,
friends, it does not seem so special to me, then
you can continue, the
company is not a bad company,
we will see the profits of the company continuously
increasing, if we
talk about the balance sheet of this company, you people will see it to be
very wonderful, the
result of the company which is of 16 crores, it can be seen increasing by more than
10 times, the
business of this Android company is
amazing, if we
talk about the career, then the profits of the company have been
seen increasing, if the profit is increasing due to the debt of the company, the
reserves are not
increasing  So definitely there would have been a
matter of taking some tension there, so whoever has a
company, if it is a bad company then they should
control it for the long term and
whoever wants to buy a new vehicle then why do I
feel that you people should keep a distance from this company,
if we talk about its
promoter holding, then now you can see
that the Delhi based company sitting with an unclear 75% stake in this company will
strengthen the company, so definitely the biggest
loss will be of Vinegar or he should
not take any such wrong step which will cause loss to the company,
after this if we
talk about approximately four and a half percent, then approximately six and a half and if we
talk about the public, then
when will we see around fifteen percent, if we talk about the
shareholding pattern,
profit and loss treatment of the company,
then I would have seen all the parameters of the company good,
so those who have it, then they should do
Holi, if we talk about the next company,
then for Edifice, you all would know that
after the 2019,
we
saw pressure in all the life insurance companies, but this company is
very good in the long term  You will
see a lot of people running away. If we
talk about this company, then I
need to tell you about the fundamentals. You all
know how fundamental the company is. You can
see the colors. So, whoever has this company,
they should definitely continue for the long term.
If we talk about the next
company, then actually you all would know that
this company is also very fundamentally
strong. If we talk about this, you will
get to see 245 products of this company in everyone's house. Apart from this, if we talk about the next
company, then you people would see here that the
fundamentals of the company are not good.
If we talk about actual or like
Lombard General Insurance, then you people should continue with
these companies. My policy is that it has a
plane. Apart from this, if we talk about the
next company, then you all would
know that today this company is going to
present its numbers. If due to some reason
or if the numbers of this company are bad or rapid or a little flat, then due to that reason, if the numbers of this company are bad or rapid, then
due to that reason,
if the numbers of this company are  If there is a fall in the shares, then
you people should invest in the shares of this company with a buy on defeated basis for the
long term. This is
my personal
opinion. If we talk about its market cap, then you
people can see here that the last step of the
company is visible. So whoever has
this company, then they do
not need to be afraid of the fall at all. In the coming time,
you people will see the business of this company growing at a very fast
pace,
due to which there will be momentum in the city. Simple things, so
friends, these were some updates which you might have liked, so
please like this video. If you are
new to the channel, then please subscribe to the channel.
And friends, this
video was only and only educational and there was
no light recommendation here.
Thank you very much.